# Sufyan Jami

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

### **Profile**

Passionate software developer who has a love for writing clean, concise and efficient code. Some technologies I like working with: React, Java, C#, JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, etc. My portfolio showcases projects I have worked on and my passion for computer science.

## **Employment History**

#### ASP.NET Core Developer, Canadian Bar Association, Remote

JANUARY 2023 - PRESENT

- Worked with various teams weekly to understand feature requirements and implemented them using Kentico 13.
- Enhanced user-experience when adding features while keeping the integrity of the software.
- Thoroughly tested each feature in various scenarios to ensure the best user experience and accessibility.

#### Tier 2 Forms Programmer, PBS Systems Inc, Calgary

APRIL 2019 - JANUARY 2023

- Managed programming for new dealership setups, created tailored solutions.
- Automated important parts of the process to boost team productivity.
- Guided junior programmers through training, code reviews, and provided documentation for learning.
- Created various process documents to help new hires and team members work more efficiently.

## Website Developer, All-In-One Digital, Calgary

DECEMBER 2018 - APRIL 2019

- Designed and Developed 10+ custom websites from start to finish.
- Worked with stakeholders to meet their needs and provide solutions.
- Implemented Search Engine Optimization.

## **Education**

Information Technology - Major in Software Development, Southern Alberta Institute of Technology (SAIT), Calgary

SEPTEMBER 2016 - JULY 2018

#### **Details**

Calgary

587-437-7834

sufijami9@gmail.com

#### Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

**Skills** 

React

Java

C#

JavaScript

Python

SQL

HTML & CSS

Node.js

Web Development

**Unit Testing** 

Debugging

Version Control/Git

APIs and Libraries

Problem Solving

Microsoft Office